ELIJAH CANNON

SOFTWARE ENGINEER

(801) 643-1098

| cclayelijah@gmail.com |

Layton, UT 84040

github.com/cclayelijah

Passionate software engineer with 2 years of professional web development experience. Have been studying Object Oriented Programming and Full-Stack development in classes and on my own since 2016. Assisted in development and maintenance of hundreds of custom websites at i4 Solutions to give clients a competitive edge. Implemented CRM technologies to boost customer satisfaction. Graduate of Associate of Science and current student of Computer Science at Weber State University. Graduate of IT and Software Development at Davis Technical College.

EXPERIENCE

Freelance WorkWeb Developer

Kaysville, UT 03.2020 - Present

TEDXBOUNTIFUL.COM

Designed and built the TEDx website for Bountiful City on Wordpress. Adjusted work as needed to satisfy the client.

TRUEREVIEWGURU.COM

Designed and built the website for myself as a side project. Learning SEO best practices to drive traffic and boost clicks.

I4 SolutionsSupport Technician

Woods Cross, UT 03.2019 - 03.2020

Established and implemented a support ticket software in the company to keep track of support related issues, boosting efficiency and customer satisfaction. Assisted in development and maintenance of over 1000 professional websites including:

DOMINATORHOOP.COM
COMPLETECOMMUNICATIONS.COM

MARSHALLRADIO.COM PACKWHEEL.COM

Papa Murphy's General Manager Farmington, UT 09.2017 - 12.2018

Supervised all work in the building. Cut costs and delivered highquality results. Conducted team meetings. Managed Inventory. Measured profits. Managed work schedules. Drove employee growth in a positive environment.

CERTIFICATIONS

MTA: Networking Fundamentals CompTIA IT Fundamentals Microsoft Office Excel 2013

SECURITY CLEARANCE

US Secret Security Clearance Status: Active 10/2020 - 10-2030

SKILLS

- GITHUB & GIT VERSION CONTROL
- OBJECT ORIENTED PROGRAMMING
- C++, JAVA, C# & .NET CORE 2.0
- DB DESIGN, MYSQL & MONGODB
- NODEJS, REACT, & NATIVE
- FLEXBOX & BOOTSTRAP CSS
- WORDPRESS & TITANIUM CMS
- DEBUGGING/TROUBLESHOOTING
- MVC DESIGN & IMPLEMENTATION

EDUCATION

WEBER STATE UNIVERSITY

Associate of Science - 2020 General Studies Bachelor of Science - 2022 Computer Science (Major) Entrepreneurship (Minor) Studied Java, C/C++, Databases, MySQL, HTML/CSS/JS, Etc.

DAVIS TECHNICAL COLLEGE

Information Technology & Software Development - 2018

Studied Computer Networking, Cyber Security, OS, Web Dev (HTML5, CSS3, JS, PHP, MySQL, ASP.NET Core 2.0, & ReactJS), DB Design, and Object Oriented Programming (VB, Java, & C#).